{
    "subject": "resource/Nenad_Bogdanovi\u0107",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107",
    "human_readable": "The name of Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107 is Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9760914444923401,
            "question": "What is Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9673193693161011,
            "question": "Does the name 'Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107' refer to someone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9376540184020996,
            "question": "What does the statement 'The name of Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107 is Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107' imply about the individual?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9208372235298157,
            "question": "If you were to introduce Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107, what would you say his name is?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8551973104476929,
            "question": "Is there any ambiguity in the information provided about Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.792004406452179,
            "question": "Is Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107 a unique individual?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.758938729763031,
            "question": "What type of information is being conveyed about Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7589161992073059,
            "question": "What can be said about the identity of Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107 based on the given information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6995248198509216,
            "question": "How would you summarize the key fact about Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6865651607513428,
            "question": "Can you think of other ways to express the same information about Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107 is Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4313_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you summarize the key fact about Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4313_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can be said about the identity of Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107 based on the given information?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4313_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of information is being conveyed about Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4313_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4313_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4313_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4313_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4313_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4313_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4313_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4313_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4313_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4313_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4313_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while the documents contain information about a person named Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107, none of them mention his surname as simply \"Bogdanovi\u0107\" without any additional names or titles. In fact, one document mentions \"Nenad Bogdanovic scores a career high 19 points (2006)\", which suggests that the correct spelling of the name is indeed \"Bogdanovic\", not just \"Bogdanovi\u0107\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents confirms that Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107's name is indeed spelled as \"Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the name \"Nenad Bogdanovi\u0107\" already matches a well-known artist, which suggests that it might be correct.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}